revenews.com 2016-05-15

# ReveNews Privacy Policy | Revenews.com by Affiliate Summit

AFFILIATE SUMMIT, INC. all its related web sites (â€œAFFILIATE SUMMITâ€) Privacy Policy

PLEASE NOTE: OUR PRIVACY POLICY CHANGES FROM TIME TO TIME AND CHANGES ARE EFFECTIVE UPON POSTING. PLEASE CHECK BACK FREQUENTLY FOR UPDATES AS IT IS YOUR SOLE RESPONSIBILITY TO BE AWARE OF CHANGES. AFFILIATE SUMMIT DOES NOT PROVIDE NOTICES OF CHANGES IN ANY MANNER OTHER THAN BY POSTING THE CHANGES AT THIS WEB SITE.

IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY PLEASE DO NOT PROVIDE ANY INFORMATION TO AFFILIATE SUMMIT OR USE ANY OF THE SERVICES OR PRODUCTS OFFERED OR PROVIDED ON ANY OF THE WEB SITES REFERRED TO IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY.

The information collection, use, and dissemination practices of AFFILIATE SUMMIT:

This policy applies to AFFILIATE SUMMITâ€™s collection, use, storage and disclosure of information by AFFILIATE SUMMIT on its (a) websites, including all its divisions, subsidiaries and related companies (collectively, the â€œWebsitesâ€), (b) on various third party websites, and (c) to AFFILIATE SUMMITâ€™s other information collection, including the purchase of customer lists from third parties. AFFILIATE SUMMIT is not responsible for the information collection or privacy practices of third web sites or applications.

1\. Collection of Information.

1.1 Survey Information.

AFFILIATE SUMMIT collects information from individuals by various methods, including, but not limited to, when an individual voluntarily completes an AFFILIATE SUMMIT survey, order form, or a registration page either online or offline, or by means of online or offline surveys, order forms, or registration pages operated by third parties (collectively, a â€œSurveyâ€). (As used herein, â€œonlineâ€ means using the Internet, including the Websites, and related technologies, and â€œofflineâ€ means by methods other than online, including in person, in the postal mail, using telephones and cell phones, and other similar means.) In the Surveys, AFFILIATE SUMMIT or a third party (a â€œThird Partyâ€) may ask an individual to provide various information to AFFILIATE SUMMIT, which may include his or her name, email address, street address, zip code, telephone numbers (including cell phone numbers and carriers), birth date, gender, salary range, education and marital status, occupation, social security number, employment information, personal and online interests, and such other information as may be requested from time to time (together, â€œSurvey Informationâ€). AFFILIATE SUMMIT may also collect information concerning an individual from another source and uses that information in combination with information provided from this web site. Completing the Surveys is completely voluntary, and individuals are under no obligation to provide Survey Information to AFFILIATE SUMMIT or Third Party, but an individual may receive incentives from AFFILIATE SUMMIT or a Third Party in exchange for providing Survey Information to AFFILIATE SUMMIT.

1.2 Third Party List Information.

AFFILIATE SUMMIT collects information from individuals when an individual provides information to a third party and AFFILIATE SUMMIT subsequently purchases, licenses, or otherwise acquires the information from the third party (the â€œSellerâ€). Such purchased information may include, but is not limited to, an individualâ€™s name, email address, street address, zip code, telephone numbers (including cell phone numbers and carriers), birth date, gender, salary range, education and marital status, occupation, industry of employment, personal and online interests, and such other information as the individual may have provided to the Seller (together, â€œThird Party List Informationâ€). When acquiring Third Party List Information, AFFILIATE SUMMIT seeks assurances from the Seller that the Seller has a right to transfer the Third Party List Information to AFFILIATE SUMMIT and that the Seller has a right to provide offers from advertisers to the individuals whose personal information is included on the Sellerâ€™s list.

1.3 Other Information.

Other occasions when AFFILIATE SUMMIT obtains information from individuals include (1) when an individual is making a claim for a prize or seeking to redeem an incentive offered by AFFILIATE SUMMIT or by a third party, (2) when an individual requests assistance through AFFILIATE SUMMIT customer service department, and (3) when an individual voluntarily subscribes to a AFFILIATE SUMMIT service or newsletter (together, â€œOther Informationâ€).

1.4 Cookies, Pixel Tags, and Other Info Collected Using Technology.

AFFILIATE SUMMIT currently uses cookie and pixel tag technology to associate certain Internet-related information about an individual with information about the individual in our database. Additionally, AFFILIATE SUMMIT may use other new and evolving sources of information in the future (together, â€œTechnology Informationâ€).

(a) Cookies.

A cookie is a small amount of data stored on the hard drive of the individualâ€™s computer that allows AFFILIATE SUMMIT to identify the individual with his or her corresponding data that resides in AFFILIATE SUMMIT database. You may read more about cookies at http://cookiecentral.com. Individuals who use the Websites need to accept cookies in order to use all of the features and functionality of the Websites.

(b) Pixel Tags.

A pixel tag is programming code that can be used to display an image on a web page (by using an programming function â€” see http://truste.org for more information), but can also be used to transfer an individualâ€™s unique user identification (often in the form of a cookie) to a database and associate the individual with previously acquired information about an individual in a database. This allows AFFILIATE SUMMIT to track certain web sites an individual visits online.

(c) New Technology.

The use of technology on the Internet, including cookies and web beacons, is rapidly evolving, as is AFFILIATE SUMMITâ€™s use of new and evolving technology. As a result, AFFILIATE SUMMIT strongly encourages individuals to revisit this policy for any updates regarding its use of technology.

1.5 Outside Information.

AFFILIATE SUMMIT may receive information about individuals from third parties or from other sources of information outside of AFFILIATE SUMMIT including information located in public databases (â€œOutside Informationâ€).

1.6 Individual Information.

As used herein, Individual Information means Survey Information, Third Party List Information, Other Information, Technology Information, and Outside Information, and any other information AFFILIATE SUMMIT gathers or receives about individuals.

1.7 No Information Collected from Children.

AFFILIATE SUMMIT will never knowingly collect any personal information about children under the age of 13. If AFFILIATE SUMMIT obtains actual knowledge that it has collected personal information about a child under the age of 13, that information will be immediately deleted from our database. Because it does not collect such information, AFFILIATE SUMMIT has no such information to use or to disclose to third parties. AFFILIATE SUMMIT has designed this policy in order to comply with the Childrenâ€™s Online Privacy Protection Act (â€œCOPPAâ€).

1.8 Credit Card Information.

AFFILIATE SUMMIT may in certain cases collect credit card numbers and related information, such as the expiration date of the card (â€œCredit Card Informationâ€) when an individual places an order from AFFILIATE SUMMIT. When the Credit Card Information is submitted to AFFILIATE SUMMIT, such information is encrypted and is protected with SSL encryption software. AFFILIATE SUMMIT will use the Credit Card Information for purposes of processing and completing the purchase transaction, and the Credit Card Information will be disclosed to third parties only as necessary to complete the purchase transaction.

2\. Use of Individual Information.

2.1 Discretion to Use Information.

THE COMPANY MAY USE INDIVIDUAL INFORMATION FOR ANY LEGALLY PERMISSIBLE PURPOSE IN COMPANYâ€™S SOLE DISCRETION.

The following paragraphs in Section 2 describe how AFFILIATE SUMMIT currently uses Individual Information, but AFFILIATE SUMMIT may change or broaden its use at any time. As noted below, AFFILIATE SUMMIT may update this policy from time to time. AFFILIATE SUMMIT may use Individual Information to provide promotional offers to individuals by means of email advertising, telephone marketing, direct mail marketing, online banner advertising, and package stuffers, among other possible uses.

2.2 Email.

AFFILIATE SUMMIT uses Individual Information to provide newsletters and promotional offers by email to individuals. AFFILIATE SUMMIT may maintain separate email lists for different purposes. If email recipients wish to end their email subscription from a particular list, they need to follow the instructions at the end of each email message to unsubscribe from the particular list. To unsubscribe from all AFFILIATE SUMMIT email lists, a person must send an email to unsubscribe@affiliatesummit.com.

2.2(a) Content of Email Messages.

In certain commercial email messages sent by AFFILIATE SUMMIT, an advertiserâ€™s name will appear in the â€œFrom:â€ line but hitting the â€œReplyâ€ button will cause a reply email to be sent to AFFILIATE SUMMIT. The â€œSubject:â€ line of AFFILIATE SUMMIT email messages will usually contain a line provided from the advertiser to AFFILIATE SUMMIT.

2.2(b) Solicited Email.

AFFILIATE SUMMIT only sends email to individuals who have agreed on the Websites to receive email from AFFILIATE SUMMIT or to individuals who have agreed on third party websites to receive email from third parties such as AFFILIATE SUMMIT. AFFILIATE SUMMIT does not send unsolicited email messages. As a result, statutes requiring certain formatting for unsolicited email are not applicable to AFFILIATE SUMMIT email messages.

2.3 Direct Mail and Telemarketing.

AFFILIATE SUMMIT uses Individual Information to advertise, directly or indirectly, to individuals using direct mail marketing or telemarketing using telephones and cell phones.

2.4 Profiles of Individuals.

AFFILIATE SUMMIT uses Individual Information to make a profile of an individual. A profile can be created by combining Survey Information and Third Party List Information with other sources of Individual Information such as information obtained from public databases.

2.5 Storage of Individual Information.

AFFILIATE SUMMIT stores the Individual Information in a database on AFFILIATE SUMMIT computers and Third Party computers. Our computers and our trusted third party provider computers have security measures (such as a firewall) in place to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under AFFILIATE SUMMITâ€™s control. Not withstanding such measures, AFFILIATE SUMMIT cannot guarantee that its security measures will prevent AFFILIATE SUMMIT or its third party providersâ€™ computers from being illegally accessed, and the Individual Information on them stolen or altered.

3\. Dissemination of Individual Information.

3.1 Sale or Transfer to Third Parties.

AFFILIATE SUMMIT MAY SELL OR TRANSFER INDIVIDUAL INFORMATION TO THIRD PARTIES FOR ANY PURPOSE IN AFFILIATE SUMMITâ€™S SOLE DISCRETION.

3.2 Order Fulfillment.

AFFILIATE SUMMIT will transfer Individual Information to third parties when necessary to provide a product or service that a person orders from such third party while using AFFILIATE SUMMIT web sites or when responding to offers provided by AFFILIATE SUMMIT.

3.3 Legal Process.

AFFILIATE SUMMIT may disclose Individual Information to respond to subpoenas, court orders, and other legal processes.

3.4 Summary Data.

AFFILIATE SUMMIT may sell or transfer non-individualized information, such as summary or aggregated anonymous information about all persons or sub-groups of persons.

3.5 Access.

Individuals have access to their Individual Information collected to provide an opportunity for an individual to correct, amend, or delete such information. Access can be obtained by contacting legal@affiliatesummit.com. AFFILIATE SUMMIT may also grant advertising clients and email services providersâ€™ access to an individualâ€™s email address to verify the origin of the Individual Information collected.

4\. Privacy Practices of Third Parties.

4.1 Advertiser cookies and web beacons.

Advertising agencies, merchants, and other companies (together, â€œAdvertisersâ€) who place advertisements on the Websites and on the Internet generally may use their own cookies, web beacons, and other technology to collect information about individuals. AFFILIATE SUMMIT does not control Advertisersâ€™ use of such technology and AFFILIATE SUMMIT has no responsibility for the use of such technology to gather information about individuals.

4.2 Links.

The Websites and email messages sometimes contain hypertext links to the web sites of third parties. AFFILIATE SUMMIT is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other web sites. Linked web sites may contain links to web sites maintained by third parties. Such links are provided for your convenience and reference only. AFFILIATE SUMMIT does not operate or control in any respect any information, software, products or services available on such third party web sites. The inclusion of a link to a web site does not imply any endorsement of the services or the site, its contents, or its sponsoring organization.

4.3 Affiliated Companies.

AFFILIATE SUMMIT may disclose, transfer, and sell Individual Information to entities affiliated with AFFILIATE SUMMIT in AFFILIATE SUMMITâ€™s discretion.

5\. Unsubscribe Procedures.

If you wish to discontinue receiving email messages from AFFILIATE SUMMIT, you have several options:

(a) Unsubscribe from one email list.  
To unsubscribe from a particular list, either (1) send an email to unsubscribe@affiliatesummit.com or (2) follow the instructions in each newsletter or promotional email message sent by AFFILIATE SUMMIT.

(b) Unsubscribe from all of AFFILIATE SUMMITâ€™s email lists.  
We reserve the right to add Individual Information to multiple lists maintained by AFFILIATE SUMMIT. To globally unsubscribe from all of AFFILIATE SUMMITâ€™s lists, send an email to unsubscribe@affiliatesummit.com.

6\. California User Consumer Rights.

In accordance with California Civil Code Sec. 1789.3, California resident users are entitled to know that they may file grievances and complaints with California Department of Consumer Affairs, 400 R Street, STE 1080, Sacramento, CA 95814; or by phone at 916-445-1254 or 800-952-5210; or by email to dca@dca.ca.gov.

For more information about protecting your privacy, you may wish to visit: www.ftc.gov

If you have questions about this policy, please contact us at legal@affiliatesummit.com
